isurveyworld.com 2018-06-29

# None

### Last updated: 05/01/2018

## What personally identifiable information does IsurveyWorld collect from me? 

### "IsurveyWorld collects information in several ways from different parts of our network of ebsites. Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, IsurveyWorld asks for your name, email, gender, address, zip code, occupation, household information and personal terests. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Once you register, you are no longer anonymous to IsurveyWorld and you can access the various protected areas of the site.

## What are cookies and how does iSurveyWorld use them? 

### A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, iSurveyWorld may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. Some areas on iSurveyWorld where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable may require that you accept cookies. This avoids you having to enter your login information many times in one day. From time to time, we may use third party cookies or web beacons to observe your behavior across multiple websites. We share the information we gather with third parties who serve targeted advertisements to you based on your browsing behaviors. These advertisements are served by multiple third party websites, visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Whenever iSurveyWorld collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this privacy Policy on that page. " Digital Fingerprinting. Generally, digital fingerprinting assigns a unique identifier to

## Digital Fingerprinting.

### Generally, digital fingerprinting assigns a unique identifier to your device or computer based upon the device’s or computer’s technical settings, characteristics and IP Address. iSurveyWorld uses digital fingerprinting technology for quality control and validation purposes and fraud detection and/or prevention, including, without limitation, identifying duplicate or fraudulent respondents. iSurveyWorld may implement and use digital fingerprinting directly or through a third party vendor.

## US-EU Safe Harbor

### We comply with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework (“Safe Harbor”), which relates to the collection, use and retention of Personal Information collected from users in the European Union. We adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program and the Safe Harbor Principles, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor Any questions or concerns about our privacy practices should be sent to the address or email below. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding the use and disclosure of Personal Information in accordance with the provisions of this Policy.If any complaints cannot be resolved between you and iSurveyWorld, we have agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of JAMS to resolve disputes pursuant to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. EU residents with unresolved complaints may refer them to the JAMS as described at http://www.jamsadr.com/file-safe-harbor-claim/. 

## Age Requirementa

### This Site is neither directed at nor intended for use by children under the age of 16. Further, we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 16. If we learn that we have inadvertently done so, we will promptly delete it and we will remove the child from any mailing lists, registrations, or other means of contacting the child. Do not access or use iSurveyWorld unless you are at least 13 years old or older. 

## Who is collecting information and for what purpose? 

### "iSurveyWorld collects valuable information which assists in developing new products and services. When you are on a iSurveyWorld site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with iSurveyWorld alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than iSurveyWorld, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service.   
Promotions that run on IsurveyClub may be sponsored by companies other than iSurveyWorld or may be co-sponsored by iSurveyWorld and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you do not want your data to be shared.   
Any Sensitive Information (i.e. personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or information specifying the sex life of the individual) will be treated with additional care. If iSurveyWorld intends to disclose such information to a third party or use it for a different purpose than originally collected, then you will be expressly asked permission prior to any such disclosure.   
Please be aware that iSurveyWorld advertisers or websites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those websites linked to iSurveyWorld are not covered by this privacy statement. "

## With whom does iSurveyWorld share my information? 

### "As a general rule, iSurveyWorld will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or User Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.   
The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed. Business Partners & Sponsors:  
iSurveyWorld may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. If any personal data about you were ever to be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data.  
Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give iSurveyWorld permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your email address will be shared. If more information will be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer.  
From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you opt-in to receive information from these third parties, iSurveyWorld will (with your permission) share your name and email address with them.  
Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate: Under confidentiality agreements, iSurveyWorld may match user information with third party data. Also, IsurveyWorld discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 45% of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. Other: iSurveyWorld may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating iSurveyWorld's Terms of Service or may be causing injuryto or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) iSurveyWorld's rights or property, other IsurveyWorld users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. IsurveyWorld may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services."

## What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information? 

### "Only iSurveyWorld (or agents working on behalf of iSurveyWorld and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those iSurveyWorld services that require registration in order to participate. iSurveyWorld does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service. "

##  What is iSurveyWorld's policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information? 

### You may edit your iSurveyWorld Account Information and your public iSurveyWorld Profile at any time by using your iSurveyWorld ID and password. Your iSurveyWorld account can be deleted or deactivated. When you leave the Panel, are removed, or the Panel is closed, we will delete all your contact details, together with any other information that could be used to identify you, keeping only anonymous responses to surveys that you participated in.

## What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information? 

### "Your iSurveyWorld Account Information and iSurveyWorld Profile are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. iSurveyWorld will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your iSurveyWorld account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. We encrypt all your personal information transmission using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Access to this information is limited to only the employees who need it in order to perform their job function (e.g. Customer Service Representatives). Whenever iSurveyWorld handles personal information as described above, regardless of where this occurs, iSurveyWorld takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, iSurveyWorld cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems."

## Opt-out of email communications

### You may opt-out of email communications by clicking the unsubscribe link in any email you receive from us.Please contact support@isurveyworld.com for further instructions about deleting or deactivating your iSurveyWorld account.

## What else should I know about my privacy? 

### "Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online."

## Additional information 

### Questions regarding this statement should be directed to support@isurveyworld.com
